[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nine years after invading Afghanistan, this country began withdrawing its troops in 1988.", "correct_answer": "USSR", "incorrect_answers": ["Iran", "Great Britain", "Pakistan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ginseng is widely used in traditional Chinese medicine. What is the meaning of the Chinese phrase renshen, from which the English word ginseng originated?", "correct_answer": "Man root", "incorrect_answers": ["Power root", "Fast growing", "Promoting life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter has the largest planetary atmosphere in the Solar System.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these hobbies is the hacky sack used?", "correct_answer": "Circle kicking", "incorrect_answers": ["Network security hacking", "Hiking", "Tourism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The action in the 2006 movie Babel takes place in four countries. Which of these countries is not featured in the movie?", "correct_answer": "Egypt", "incorrect_answers": ["The United States", "Japan", "Morocco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Wagner, the first American to produce lager beer, had a brewery in which state?", "correct_answer": "Pennsylvania", "incorrect_answers": ["New Jersey", "New York", "Maine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these modern composers was born in South Africa?", "correct_answer": "Niel van der Watt", "incorrect_answers": ["John Williams", "Andrew Lloyd Webber", "Alex Wurman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This gland is shaped like a butterfly and helps regulate energy in the body.", "correct_answer": "thyroid", "incorrect_answers": ["parathyroid", "adrenal", "thymus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first professional athlete in baseball history to hit a home run and score a touchdown in the same week?", "correct_answer": "Jim Thorpe", "incorrect_answers": ["Bo Jackson", "Mel Hubbard", "Deion Sanders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2006 Milla Jovovich film uses the basic premise of John Cassavetess 1980 film Gloria.", "correct_answer": "Ultraviolet", "incorrect_answers": ["Doom", "BloodRayne", "Resident Evil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these was Tom Cruises feature film debut?", "correct_answer": "Endless Love", "incorrect_answers": ["The Outsiders", "Losin It", "Taps"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the mean temperature on the surface of Mercury?", "correct_answer": "333 degrees Fahrenheit / 167 degrees Celsius", "incorrect_answers": ["-10 degrees Fahrenheit / -23 degrees Celsius", "212 degrees Fahrenheit / 100 degrees Celsius", "1,500 degrees Fahrenheit / 815 degrees Celsius"]}]